Guide to the Northern Pacific Railway Company Records 1870-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Engineering Department, 1870-1968; Subgroup 1; 165.25 linear feet and 14 oversize volumes
  - Other Construction Projects and Unidentified, 1881-1968; Series XXI; 8.5 linear feet and 1 oversize volume
    This series contains both unbound material and bound volumes from various construction projects of the Northern Pacific Railway Company as well as some materials that could not be authoritatively identified with existing organizational series. The series is divided into ten subseries: (1) Ainsworth Mill (BC), (2) Anacortes Improvements (Washington), (3) Butte Quarry (Montana), (4) Columbia River Bridge No. 1, Pasco-Kennewick, (Washington), (5) J.W. Kendrick: Minnesota/North Dakota/Montana construction, (6) Lewistown Outside Yards (Idaho), (7) Seattle Extension, (8) Seattle Wharf Work, (9) Superior Ore Dock (Wisconsin), and (10) Unidentified. Materials in this series include outgoing correspondence primarily documenting construction projects (subcontractor and vendor agreements) and transportation passes. Financial records in this series generally present construction estimates and actual expenses, cash books, and activity logs.
    - Ainsworth (BC) Mill, 1883-1884; Subseries 1; 1 bound volume
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1883-11 - 1884-08 (Box-volume 249/352)
    - Anacortes Improvements (Washington), 1890-1891; Subseries 2; 2 bound volumes
      - Outgoing Correspondence, H.C. Estep, 1890-08 - 1891-01 (Box-volume 249/353)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, C.E. Spring, 1891-01 - 1891-06 (Box-volume 249/354)
    - Butte Quarry (Montana), 1894-1898; Subseries 3; 1 bound volume
      - General Correspondence, 1883-10-12 - 1883-11-27 (Box-folder 250/1)
    - Columba River Bridge No. 1, Pasco-Kennewick (Washington), 1886-1909; Subseries 4; 0.75 linear feet
      - General Correspondence, 1905-12-30 - 1906-03-09 (Box-folder 250/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1906-03-10 - 1906-07-31 (Box-folder 250/3)
      - Car Reports, 1905-09 - 1906-11 (Box-folder 250/4)
      - Expense Bills, 1905-05 - 1905-09 (Box-folder 250/5)
      - Expense Bills, 1905-09 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 250/6)
      - Estimates, 1886-06 - 1886-12 (Box-folder 250/7)
      - Estimates, 1887-01 - 1887-05 (Box-folder 250/8)
      - Materials, 1905-05 - 1905-12 (Box-folder 250/9)
      - Materials, 1906-01 - 1906-11 (Box-folder 250/10)
      - Force Reports, 1905-06 - 1906-01 (Box-folder 250/11)
      - Force Reports, 1906-02 - 1906-11 (Box-folder 250/12)
      - Requisitions, 1905-05 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 251/1)
      - Inventory, 1905-06 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 251/2)
      - Overtime Record, 1905-08 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 251/3)
      - Date on Revised Classification, 1909-01-13 (Box-folder 251/4)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-09 - 1906-02 (Box-volume 252/355)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1906-02 - 1906-08 (Box-volume 252/356)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-06 - 1905-07 (Box-volume 252/357)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-07 (Box-volume 252/358)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-07 - 1905-08 (Box-volume 252/359)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-08 (Box-volume 252/360)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-08 - 1905-09 (Box-volume 252/361)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-09 (Box-volume 252/362)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-09 - 1905-11 (Box-volume 252/363)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-11 - 1906-03 (Box-volume 252/364)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1906-03 - 1906-08 (Box-volume 252/365)
    - J. W. Kendrick: Minnesota/North Dakota/Montana Construction, 1886-1887; Subseries 5; 1 bound volume
      - Outgoing Correspondence, Telegrams, 1886-10 - 1887-12 (Box-volume 252/366)
    - Lewiston Outside Yards (Idaho), 1906-1909; Subseries 6; 0.5 linear feet
      - General Correspondence, 1906-02 - 1906-06 (Box-folder 253/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1906-07 - 1906-08 (Box-folder 253/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1906-09 - 1907-02 (Box-folder 253/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-03 - 1907-10 (Box-folder 253/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-11 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 253/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-06 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 253/6)
      - General Correspondence, New Buildings, 1906-09 - 1908-06 (Box-folder 253/7)
      - Maps, 1907-02 - 1908-07 (Box-folder 253/8)
    - Seattle Extension, (Swinomish Reservation), undated; Subseries 7; 2 bound volumes
      - Record of Construction, undated (Box-volume 254/367)
      - Index to Volume 367, undated (Box-volume 254/368)
    - Seattle Wharf Work, 1900; Subseries 8; 1 bound volume
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1900-09 - 1900-11 (Box-volume 254/369)
    - Superior Ore Docks (Wisconsin), 1906-1914; Subseries 9; 2.25 linear feet
      - General Correspondence, 1912-09 - 1913-02 (Box-folder 255/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1913-03 - 1913-07 (Box-folder 255/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1913-08 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 255/3)
      - General Correspondence, Pilings, 1912-11 - 1913-02 (Box-folder 255/4)
      - General Correspondence, Dock Substructure, 1912-10 - 1913-08 (Box-folder 255/5)
      - General Correspondence, Dock Superstructure, 1912-09 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 255/6)
      - General Correspondence, Cement and Gravel, 1913-02 - 1913-11 (Box-folder 255/7)
      - General Correspondence, Grassy Point Bridge, 1913-01 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 255/8)
      - General Correspondence, Demurrage, 1913-01 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 255/9)
      - General Correspondence, Approach Trestle, 1912-09 - 1912-12 (Box-folder 256/1)
      - General Correspondence, Approach Trestle, 1913-01 - 1913-09 (Box-folder 256/2)
      - General Correspondence, Invoices and Bills, 1912-11 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 256/3)
      - General Correspondence, Payroll, 1912-11 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 256/4)
      - General Correspondence, Accounting Department, 1912-10 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 256/5)
      - General Correspondence, Rights of Way/Bill of Materials, 1912-10 - 1913-11 (Box-folder 256/6)
      - General Correspondence, Office of Sanitation, 1912-10 - 1913-11 (Box-folder 256/7)
      - General Correspondence, Freight Charges, 1912-05, 1912-12 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 256/8)
      - General Correspondence, Time and Expense Checks, 1912-10 - 1913-04, 1913-10 (Box-folder 256/9)
      - General Correspondence, Grading and Approach, 1913-01 - 1913-09 (Box-folder 256/10)
      - General Correspondence, Applications for Work, 1907, 1912-09 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 256/11)
      - General Correspondence, Electrical Equipment, Contract with Burgess Electric Company, 1913-02 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 256/12)
      - General Correspondence, Northern Power Company, Crossing Power Lines, 1912-11 - 1913-05 (Box-folder 256/13)
      - General Correspondence, Plans and Specifications, 1912-11 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 256/14)
      - General Correspondence, Transportation Passes, 1912-09 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 256/15)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1912-09 - 1913-03 (Box-folder 257/1)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1913-04 - 1913-06 (Box-folder 257/2)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1913-07 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 257/3)
      - Return of Time, 1912-11 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 257/4)
      - Expenses, 1912-10 - 1913-02 (Box-folder 257/5)
      - Expenses, 1913-03 - 1913-06 (Box-folder 257/6)
      - Expenses, 1913-07 - 1913-09 (Box-folder 257/7)
      - Expenses, 1913-10 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 257/8)
      - Expenses, 1912-12 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 258/1)
      - Inventory of Instruments, 1912-11 - 1913-09 (Box-folder 258/2)
      - Payroll, 1912-10 - 1913-05, 1913-08 - 1914-01 (Box-folder 258/3)
      - Daily Report of Work, 1913-01 - 1913-02 (Box-folder 258/4)
      - Daily Report of Work, 1913-03 - 1913-05 (Box-folder 258/5)
      - Daily Report of Work, 1913-05-03 - 1913-06-14 (Box-folder 258/6)
      - Daily Report of Work, 1913-06-15 - 1913-08-15 (Box-folder 258/7)
      - Ore Docks on the Great Lakes Reports, 1912-10 - 1912-11 (Box-folder 258/8)
      - Tests of Gravel and Cement Reports, 1913-05, 1913-07 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 259/1)
      - Demurrage Bureau Reports, 1913-03 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 259/2)
      - Monthly Meteorological Reports, 1906-10 - 1907-11 (Box-folder 259/3)
      - Inspection Reports, 1912-11 - 1913-12 (Box-folder 259/4)
      - General Correspondence and Financial Records, 1912-12 - 1913-10 (Box-folder 259/5)
    - Unidentified, 1880-1968 and undated; Subseris 10; 4.0 linear feet and 1 oversize volume
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1912-12 - 1913-02 (Box-volume 260/370)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1913-02 - 1913-07 (Box-volume 260/371)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1913-04 - 1913-05 (Box-volume 261/372)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1913-04 - 1913-06 (Box-volume 261/373)
      - Financial Journal, 1883-01 - 1883-08 (Box-volume 261/374)
      - Financial Ledger, 1883-04 - 1884-01 (Box-volume 261/375)
      - Financial Ledger, 1883-05 - 1883-08 (Box-volume 261/376)
      - Financial Journal, Wisconsin Central Lines, 1886 - 1892 (Box-volume 262/377)
      - Cash Book, 1880-08 - 1882-11 (Box-volume 262/378)
      - Cash Book, 1882-04 - 1882-09 (Box-volume 262/379)
      - Cash Book, 1882-11 - 1883-02 (Box-volume 262/380)
      - Cash Book, 1883-02 - 1883-05 (Box-volume 262/381)
      - Bill Record Book, 1895-01 - 1896-12 (Box-volume 263/382)
      - Day Book, 1895-11 - 1897-11 (Box-volume 263/383)
      - Material Received, 1898-04 - 1899-02 (Box-volume 263/384)
      - Materials, 1909-07 - 1910-01 (Box-volume 263/385)
      - Time Book, Laborers, 1881-05 - 1881-07 (Box-volume 263/386)
      - Time Book, Various, 1884-10 - 1885-03 (Box-volume 263/387)
      - Time Book, 1886-04 - 1886-10 (Box-volume 264/388)
      - Time Book, Blasting Crew, 1888-06 - 1888-09 (Box-volume 264/389)
      - Time Book, 1888-04 - 1888-07 (Box-volume 264/390)
      - Time Book, Engineer and Construction Force, 1887-09 - 1887-12 (Box-volume 264/391)
      - Time Book, 1887-04 - 1887-07 (Box-volume 264/392)
      - Time Book, 1904-12 (Box-volume 264/393)
      - Force Account, 1899-07 - 1900-08 (Box-volume 264/394)
      - Force Account, 1899-07 - 1900-06 (Box-volume 265/395)
      - Work Orders and Time Reports, 1907 (Box-volume 265/396)
      - Force Report, 1899-10 - 1900-05 (Box-volume 265/397)
      - Claim Checks, 1944-11 - 1946-03 (Box-volume 265/398)
      - Ledger, Yakima and Ainsworth (Washington), 1885-07 - 1885-10 (Volume 399)
      - Financial Records, Material, 1905-08 - 1905-09 (Box-volume 266/400)
      - Supplies at Various Stations, undated (Box-volume 266/401)
      - Distribution of General Time, undated (Box-volume 266/402)
      - Estimates, 1885 (Box-volume 266/403)
      - Record of Track Laying and Grading, 1887 - 1888 (Box-volume 266/404)
      - Timber Received, 1911-01 - 1912-04 (Box-volume 266/405)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/6)
      - General Correspondence, 1948 - 1968 (Box-folder 267/7)
  - Photographs, 1882-1959; Series XXII; 2.0 linear feet and 1 oversize box
    This series contains photographs intended as a documentary record for railway operations--such as construction projects, railroad facilities, engines, and work conditions--though some promotional photographs are present as well. Photographs in this series constitute a valuable resource documenting landscapes, towns, community events, rural life, work crews, rail infrastructures, and weather events throughout the high plains and montane valleys of the central and western United States--as well as spanning eighty years of dramatic physical, economic, and social change. Materials in this series exhibit several distinct sequences of image themes. Among these are extensive Montana bridge, station, and change yard sequences (often identified by location or structural number but seldom both). Billings, Bozeman, Brockway, Circle, Glendive, Lindsay, and Missoula, Montana--and their respective outlying areas--are among the communities most significantly documented by the images in this series.
    Another extensive image sequence documents the possessions, staple crops, and vistas of Mission Valley (Montana) homestead families during the late 1920s. The Mission Valley photographs were captured for promotional purposes, as opposed to the construction and facility images that dominate this series. Another promotional image sequence includes produce being carried to market. These promotional photographs were primarily intended to convey perceptions of abundance and help the railroad sell rail accessible farm plots.
    The majority of materials in this series are identified and described individually, with reference to location and date whenever such information could be established; however, the series also includes some grouped photographs recovered from a separated collection. Photographs individually identified and described during original processing were assigned identification numbers according to the year and order in which they were processed. During reprocessing all these photographs were assigned new reference numbers to reflect their relationship within the larger collection--regardless of year--though the original numbers are noted in brackets for cross-reference.
    Photographs in boxes 396, 397, and OS1 are not individually processed. These materials are grouped by subject following the titles imposed upon them after they were seperated from the original collection and before they were donated to the K. Ross Toole Archives. The conditions and purposes under which these materials were originally separated are unknown.
    - Fourth of July celebration, Arlee, Montana, 1929; 128(XXII):1 or 70-30 (Box-folder 393/1)
    - Northern Pacific exhibition car; "Its exhibits encouraged people to buy the railroad's lands", undated; 128(XXII):2 or 71-12 (Box-folder 393/1)
    - Charlo, Montana. "Three new outfits of prospective new settlers just pulled in from Nebraska, not yet located but being shown over the Valley by Northern Pacific Agents", 1919; 128(XXII):3 or 71-20 (Box-folder 393/1)
    - Flour mill at Russell-Miller Milling Company at Sidney, Montana, 1926-07-14; 128(XXII):4 or 71-23 (Box-folder 393/2)
    - Lumber mill in Eureka, Montana, 1910; 128(XXII):5 or 71-25 (Box-folder 393/2)
    - Display of farm machinery in the Redwater District in eastern Montana, undated; 128(XXII):6 or 72-4 (Box-folder 393/2)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Roundhouse under construction in Missoula, Montana, 1923; 128(XXII):7 or 72-17 (Box-folder 393/2)
    - Amalgamated Sugar Company building located in Missoula, Montana, undated; 128(XXII):8 or 72-199 (Box-folder 393/3)
    - W.C. Howell and family in front of their home in Charlo, Montana surrounded by dairy cows, 1928; 128(XXII):9 or 72-201, [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/3)
    - Arthur Coulter and family in front of their home in Charlo, Montana with dairy cows to the right, undated; 128(XXII):10 or 72-202 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/4)
    - George Watson and faimly in front of their farm home in Charlo, Montana; Barn on left with horses and dairy cows nearby, undated; 128(XXII):11 or 72-203 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/5)
    - George Kelly family posed in field in Charlo, Montana with Mr. Kelly sitting on horse-drawn plow, 1928; 128(XXII):12 or 72-204 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/5)
    - "Truck loaded from West Coast with bee hives parked in front of the Larsen Real Estate Company and Northern Pacific Railway irrigration office in Charlo, Montana; Man on right is Bill Larsen, owner of Larsen Real Estate and Northern Pacific land promoter", 1928; 128(XXII):13 or 72-205 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/6)
    - Amos L. Gallup family posed with dairy cows in Charlo, Montana, 1928; 128(XXII):14 or 72-206, [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/6)
    - Men of the A.L. Freyberger family posed with their farm, horse teams, and cattle in Charlo, Montana, 1928-07-25; 128(XXII):15 or 72-207 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 393/7)
    - View of the Roundhouse from Waterworks Hill in Missoula, Montana, 1883; 128(XXII):16 or 73-12 (Box-folder 393/7)
    - Main lower Yellowstone canal; looking up the canal from Indian Coulee bridge, 1910-07-06; 128(XXII):17 or 75-6083 (Box-folder 393/8)
    - On dude ranch in Flathead Valley, Montana, 1930-06; 128(XXII):18 or 75-6090 (Box-folder 393/8)
    - McGiffert steam log loader, 1910; 128(XXII):19 or 76-160 (Box-folder 393/8)
    - Trainload of wartime freight moves over the line west of Missoula, Montana, undated; 128(XXII):20 or 76-208 (Box-folder 393/8)
    - Scotch making Still in Bitterroot Valley, Montana, undated; 128(XXII):21 or 76-435 (Box-folder 393/8)
    - Crow Indians at the "Villard Gold Spike Excursion," opening of the Northern Pacific Railway, 1883-09-08; 128(XXII):22 or 76-436 (Box-folder 393/9)
    - Farmer operating a horse drawn binder, which cuts the grain and ties into bundles to be shocked and thrashed, undated; 128(XXII):23 or 76-442 (Box-folder 393/9)
    - Harvesting apples in the Bitterroot Valley, Montana, 1910; 128(XXII):24 or 77-36 (Box-folder 393/9)
    - Hauling beets from Daley Farm near Hamilton, Montana, 1928-09-25; 128(XXII):25 or 77-39 (Box-folder 393/9)
    - Testing the Bismarck Bridge over the Missouri River, 1882-10-21; 128(XXII):26 or 77-238 (Box-folder 393/10)
    - End of the track near Fort Benton, Montana, undated; 128(XXII):27 or 78-308 (Box-folder 393/10)
    - Northern Pacific Railway, Orofino Branch, Whiskey Creek Bridge, Idaho, 1912; 128(XXII):28 or 80-37 (Box-folder 393/10)
    - Train wreck, undated; 128(XXII):29 or 82-195 (Box-folder 393/11)
    - Train moving past river, undated; 128(XXII):30 or 82-197 (Box-folder 393/11)
    - Derailed engine, undated; 128(XXII):31 or 82-198 (Box-folder 393/11)
    - Derailed engine, undated; 128(XXII):32 or 82-199 (Box-folder 393/11)
    - Derailed engine, undated; 128(XXII):33 or 82-200 (Box-folder 393/11)
    - Missoula Fairgrounds, cattle show, 1928; 128(XXII):34 or 82-204 (Box-folder 393/12)
    - Amalgamated Sugar Company under construction, 1928; 128(XXII):35 or 82-205 (Box-folder 393/12)
    - Northern Pacific Railway reaching the shores of Flathead Lake near Polson, Montana, 1917-12-07; 128(XXII):36 or 83-3 (Box-folder 393/12)
    - Exhibition car used in the promotion of settlement, undated; 128(XXII):37 or 83-81 (Box-folder 393/12)
    - Governor J.E. Erickson addressing a crowd in Bozeman, Montana, 1912; 128(XXII):38 or 84-150 (Box-folder 393/12)
    - Northern Pacific depot at Garrison, Montana; left: North Coast Limited #2, right: North Coast Limited #1, 1920; 128(XXII):39 or 86-0011 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - Dry farm, sorghum, Rosebud County, Montana, 1909; 128(XXII):40 or 87-0040 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - Grasshopper nymphs on woodpile, 1938; 128(XXII):41 or 87-0041 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - New oil house at the Northern Pacific Railway yard in Missoula, Montana, 1954-07-15; 128(XXII):42 or 89-299 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - New oil house at the Northern Pacific Railway yard in Missoula, Montana, 1954-07-15; 128(XXII):43 or 89-300 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - Northern Pacific Freight House in Bozeman, Montana, 1954-12-17; 128(XXII):44 or 89-301 (Box-folder 394/1)
    - Northern Pacific Freight House in Bozeman, Montana, 1953-12-17; 128(XXII):45 or 89-302 (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Freight House in Bozeman, Montana, 1953-12-17; 128(XXII):46 or 89-303 (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):47 or 89-318 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):48 or 89-319 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):49 or 89-320 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):50 or 89-321 [Negative located in folder 396/1] (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):51 or 89-322 (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Northern Pacific Yard Office in Missoula, Montana, 1959; 128(XXII):52 or 89-323 (Box-folder 394/2)
    - Along Northern Pacific Railway line in Missoula, Montana near round house, 1959; 128(XXII):53 or 89-324 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - Along Northern Pacific Railway line in Missoula, Montana near round house, 1952; 128(XXII):54 or 89-325 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - Steel building at the Missoula Northern Pacific Railway Yard, 1957-11-05; 128(XXII):55 or 89-326 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - A Northern Pacific train at the big curve near Perma, 1951; 128(XXII):56 or 89-327 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - A rock slide along the Northern Pacific line, 1954; 128(XXII):57 or 89-328 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - A rock slide along the Northern Pacific line with workers, 1954; 128(XXII):58 or 89-329 (Box-folder 394/3)
    - A rock slide near St. Regis along Northern Pacific line, 1952-02-02; 128(XXII):59 or 89-330 (Box-folder 394/4)
    - New telephone building in Salmon, Idaho, 1952-06-09; 128(XXII):60 or 89-331 (Box-folder 394/4)
    - New telephone building nearing completion in Salmon, Idaho, 1952-06-09; 128(XXII):61 or 89-332 (Box-folder 394/4)
    - "Dr. Reynolds band of ewes and lambs, south Miles City in Custer Forest (Montana), sheep wagon foreground", 1931-06-20; 128(XXII):62 or 95-20 (Box-folder 394/4)
    - Northern Pacific exhibit car, undated; 128(XXII):63 or 95-57 (Box-folder 394/4)
    - Bridge #1, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):64 or 95-156 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge #1, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):65 or 95-157 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge #2, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):66 or 95-158 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge #2, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):67 or 95-159 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Riprap at West and Bridge #2, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):68 or 95-160 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Dike and riprap at channel change, station 244, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):69 or 95-161 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Riprap on dike, station 244, 1928-06-21; 128(XXII):70 or 95-162 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Riprap at channel change, station 255, 1928-07-03; 128(XXII):71 or 95-163 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge at station 497, 1928-09-17; 128(XXII):72 or 95-164 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge at station 497, 1928-09-14; 128(XXII):73 or 95-165 (Box-folder 394/5)
    - Bridge at station 431, 1928-09-17; 128(XXII):74 or 95-166 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #12 at station 876, 1928-09-21; 128(XXII):75 or 95-167 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #16 at station 1050, 1928-09-21; 128(XXII):76 or 95-168a (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #16 at station 1050, 1928-09-21; 128(XXII):77 or 95-168b (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #17 at station 1061, 1928-09-21; 128(XXII):78 or 95-169 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #22, 1928-06-07; 128(XXII):79 or 95-170 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #22, station 1670, 1928-03-16; 128(XXII):80 or 95-171 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #23, station 1768, 1928-09-29; 128(XXII):81 or 95-172 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #23, station 1768, 1928-09-29; 128(XXII):82 or 95-173 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Bridge #23, station 1768, 1928-09-29; 128(XXII):83 or 95-174 (Box-folder 394/6)
    - Erecting Bridge #23, station 1770, 1928-04-11; 128(XXII):84 or 95-175 (Box-folder 394/7)
    - Erecting Bridge #23, station 1770, 1928-04-11; 128(XXII):85 or 95-176 (Box-folder 394/7)
    - Bridge #23, station 1770, undated; 128(XXII):86 or 95-177 (Box-folder 394/7)